

Shivansh Agarwal

Full Stack Web Developer

Professional Summary

A self-motivated and hard-working full stack web developer with proficiency in JavaScript. Adaptable and accountable team player, driven to deliver the best in any situation. Looking forward to utilizing current skillset and experience of working on projects to create a mark in the software industry and achieve organizational goals.

Projects

Adorama (Clone)

Adorama is an affordable photography, electronics, video, and camera store. They carry a large selection of camera equipment and have the best prices in the NYC area. .

Tech Stack - React | Chakra-UI | GitHub | Netlify **Features -** JSON-server | Add to cart | Carousel | Remove |
Authentication | Axios | React-Router | Private Route

It's an **Individual** project built & executed in 5days

Apollo 247(Clone) |

Apollo 24|7 is a part of the multi-specialty healthcare group Apollo Hospitals with the core belief that Expertise is for Everyone. With the launch of Apollo 24|7, the vision of founder Dr. Prathap C Reddy of removing mobility barriers from healthcare has become a reality.

Tech Stack - HTML | JavaScript | CSS | GitHub | Netlify

Features - JSON-server | Add to cart | Carousel | Remove | Functionality like remove | Quantity | Checkout | Payment It's an **Individual** project built & executed in 5 days

Work Experience

Business Development Associate BYJU'S Think & Learn Pvt. Ltd (July 2019 - December 2019)

Senior Academic Counselor Vedantu Pvt. Ltd (January 2020 – August 2021)

Sales Manager Cuemath Pvt. Ltd (September 2021 – January 2022)

My Contact

Shvnshgrwll@gmail.com

+91-9660680092

Bikaner, Rajasthan

in Shivansh Agarwal

Shvnshgrwl

Technical Skills

• React | Redux | Typescript

• Chakra UI

• Javascript | HTML | CSS

• Data Structure & Algorithms

· Git & Github

Soft Skills

Problem-Solving

Team Work

Remote Work

Adaptability

Education Background

Full Stack Web Development (Full
 Time)
 Masai School, Bengaluru
 Jan 2022 - Feb 2023

Master in Business Administration IMS, Bikaner, Rajasthan Apr 2015 - May 2017

Bachelor of Commerce
 Jain College, Bikaner, Rajasthan
 Apr 2011 - March 2015